MY ROYAL NEMESIS
Do you all remember the Star of the
Temptress? The comet that appeared
alongside the total solar eclipse three
months ago can still be seen in the
night sky. We will all feel a sense
of loss when it suddenly disappears.
So I recommend taking a photo of it now
while you still can. Unlike meteors
and shooting stars, that vanish in the
blink of an eye, this star appeared
silently and can disappear
without warning at any moment.
EPISODE 10
HOPE, DESPAIR, AND LONGING
Oh, I'm so sorry, but the chairman is
sleeping. I understand, I just can't let
you in right now. But I'll be sure to let
him know you stopped by when he wakes
up. Goodbye.
So I'm the, uh… Grand Prince that
was exiled and you're the court lady?
That's right.
The dreams mean something after all.
I'm seeing visions of our past lives.
You are.
So what's your deal? Are you in
a time slip or something?
Uh… not at all. My spirit traversed
through the ages.
That's the same thing.
No wonder you sound so old-fashioned.
But this isn't some X-Files episode.
How is this possible?
You said you believed me.
I know, I know. I'm just struggling to
make sense of it, but given the
situation…
I'll do my best.
Would you go see a doctor?
A doctor?
I just mean, it is possible that… we've
completely lost our minds. Some
professional tests would be… an
awful idea.
Does this mean that our…
trial period is done with?
Why ask me that? You're embarrassing me
Well, you know, I just wanted to make
sure I wasn't getting ahead of myself.
We have smashed our lips together enough,
I suppose the trial period no
longer makes sense.
No. So it means we're on day one
from today, right?
Promise me one thing. From now on,
there are--
No secrets between us ever.
Yeah, exactly. And if Choi Mun-do
shows up for--
I'll tell you immediately if he does.
That's right. I'm the jealous type,
understand? And I don't mean just him,
I don't want you to be involved with,
or to talk to, or to meet any guys.
Hey, how am I supposed to work then?
Half the world is male. Am I meant to
shut myself off from the world?
Well, I'm just making a point.
Anyway, given all that…
how about we go inside to finish our
conversation?
Ugh, for God's sake. Who left this here,
huh?
H-how long have you been there?
Oh, I just came up to water the
plants and missed my chance to leave.
Don't worry, do carry on.
Why is he being so nice?
I can water the plants tomorrow. But you
can't stay overnight.
Manager fellow! Such impropriety.
I can't?
Of course not.
You're right. That's a step too far
for a Joseon woman, I guess.
No, I'm no longer a Joseon woman.
From now on, I won't be stingy with
my heart, or suffer in silence.
I'll open up and give freely.
Give me more.
GIFTING HEALTH THROUGH CARE
AFFECTION
Heat in a double boiler and take it
after breakfast and dinner.
How many times have I told her
this is all marketing?
Quit the smartass comments about
marketing and don't miss a single dose.
What the hell? Is she a mind-reader?
Consider it my way of showing how much I
cherish you. Signing off.
Cherish?
I'll do it just for you.
Just took it.
I'm going to give freely from now on.
Not only my heart, but I will spend all
my money openly.
That's my girl.
Here.
Grandma, whatever you want. Just
let me know, okay? You want any clothes?
Buy yourself some first. Ugh, what
a waste of your beauty.
Oh, yeah. It is a waste. Time goes by
and you can never get it back. I'm going
to live without regrets.
I'll live life to the fullest. I'll be
generous and give openly. That's what
it means to live a good life.
This is really sweet. They said
these apples got snowed on, but they
taste great!
Oh, my little angel.
That's right. Leave apples too long
and they rot. All things spoil if
hoarded. Here, take it.
Why are you giving us these?
Well, I bought them all because they were
on sale. They said they were snowed on,
but they're actually sweet.
What's going on? Maybe they've
been poisoned.
Hilarious.
Manager fellow!
Jesus, you scared me
Here. You got me my place, you take my
deliveries. I've always wanted to
thank you for everything. There's no
manager fellow quite like you
in the world. Let us stay this way
forever.
My Gwang-nam, I was wondering where you
were. And here you are.
"My Gwang-nam?"
Here, I want you to try this. It's very
sweet.
You really want me to have this? For
free?
Of course it's free. Why would I
charge you for an apple? You think
so little of me?
Why are you suddenly being so generous?
That's not like you.
Why is that an issue? What do you mean,
it's not like me? I look pure as snow.
As long as I stay silent and do not
speak.
Who on earth told you that?
The fruit seller woman.
Let me guess, she also said you have a
sparking personality?
Can you believe this? Look, they're all
completely frozen at the bottom.
What? Frozen?
That's terrible. In my town, we wouldn't
harvest ones like that.
Oh, no. I sent them to someone already.
CHA SE-GYE
Mr. Son. Who on earth would send apples
to Mr. Cha?
A crate of apples is well known to mean
conspiracy, corruption, and acts of
collusion between politics and business.
You're looking inside?
Ms. Kim, you should watch out.
A bomb could be in there.
I think perhaps we should call
for back up instead.
Don't worry. I served in the Marines.
First Division,
A Poison Frog.
-I'd leave that alone if I were you.
-Mr. Cha, please stay back.
Don't touch it. It's mine, Son.
I'm sure it is. It's Shin Seo-ri's.
It's the second gift she's sent to me.
The second? What was the first one?
Uh, she…
got me some herbal medicine. It seems
that she cherishes me. Something
like that. You know, when you, uh, care
about someone you worry about them
and stuff.
It's more concern than affection,
if you ask me.
Concern?
About your well being. Especially your…
stamina. I think that's what she's
concerned about.
Stamina?
But even more importantly, I have an
update about the nurse.
Oh, tell me. What's going on with her?
She'll turn herself in once this is over.
Until then, she's under our protection,
sir.
Yeah? Let's avoid unnecessary bloodshed.
Be as discreet as possible.
That's all well and good, sir, but
the regime is about to change.
Regime?
Sir, please forgive me. I was wrong.
Forgive you for what? Did I punish you
for anything?
Please give me one more chance. You know
how hard I've worked for the firm all
this time.
Well now, Mun-do, the problem is no
salaried employee works that hard for
their firm, understand? You were happy to
give so much because you thought it was
yours. Oh, dear. I've worked you for too
long, I suppose. It's high time you took
things a little easier. Go to the U.S.
It'll be an opportunity for you to spend
some time with Seo-jun as his dad, before
you come back.
Grandfather's ruthless. Who'd have
thought he'd bleed Mun-do dry and ship
him off to the U.S.?
Oh, you knew already?
Do you think I was oblivious just
because I was dating? It's my job
to find out about this.
It's time you start to prepare yourself.
Since you're already in the
know, I might as well tell you. The
chairman has been working with his
attorney to have his will notarized.
Oof, he's intending to just straight up
leave it all to me in this day and age?
Let's just hold a beat for now.
Wrap up your launch and come back to
the firm with your pride intact. You've
succeeded enough to be proud of what
you've achieved.
Understood, grandfather. But I have
one condition.
A condition?
I'm calling off my engagement with
Mochang.
What?
I know that I worry you.
But I can stand on my own two feet,
you know that. I'm breaking it off.
What did I do in my past life to deserve
this? Why are both my nephew and
grandson this way?
Have you told your grandfather
about the bug?
What's the point? It'll just make him
worry.
You should still tell him. You never
know what Mun-do might do next.
I'm still nervous.
If you're nervous, imagine how he'd feel.
He's relied on him for so long.
Once Choi Mun-do leaves I won't have to
worry about him anymore. So until
then, I need to make sure grandfather
doesn't find out.
You believe he'll go without a fight?
This is where the cosmic energy lies?
Be quiet. This place is well-known
among insiders for the most accurate
readings.
Gosh. Well, um, could I get you anything
for you to drink? It's not much,
but I'll whip up some coffee with these
instant coffee sticks. Excuse me.
-I'll be right back.
-Ah, no…
Yes.
What was I thinking letting you
drag us here together. When will
you come to your senses?
Ju-mi, just think about it. Does Father
even listen to anything we say?
Does that jerk Cha Se-gye pay
any attention to us ever? Mun-do is
about to be frozen out, and you and
I have no power to do anything about
it at all. All we can do is let the holy
cosmic energy guide us.
I just don't get why we have to come to
a place like this to be guided?
So what do you suggest we do? I told
you, our lifeline is surely out there
somewhere. We're in the middle of enemy
grounds.
Cha Se-gye is this. He's the door handle
to power.
You think so?
Too bad. My place doesn't have a door
handle. Huh? You dare infiltrate my
place, you spies? Be gone, you demons.
Be gone! Out! Out!
Ew, ew. Oh, my God.
Out of here. Oh, the ancestors are angry,
yeah! The ancestral spirits are
so angry. You've enraged them! How dare
you offend them?
Oh, my God, what is this?
We're leaving, we're leaving! Stop that!
Be gone, leeches! Go, you vermin!
Mongrels!
Why did you have to get these
rotten apples. Yuck.
How could they charge me for these?
If I ever catch them, I'll make them pay
for this.
Why do I have to be punished with
hard labor? Business and
personal matters are separate, you know?
Do you not possess a conscience? Are you
trying to get paid even more money?
Wow, a second ago it was, "my Gwang-nam."
You turn with the wind. What's all
this anyway? Did Mr. Cha tell you he
likes nice girls?
No, it's just that…
Wait, what? Don't tell me you're…
Come on, it was easy to guess
with that car showing up here all the
time. I have eyes it's not hard to
notice.
You little devil.
You were playing dumb all this time.
Your Highness. It's me, Fortune Teller
Geum.
It's high time you took things a little
easier.
Go to the U.S. It'll be an opportunity
for you to spend some time with
Seo-jun as his dad before you come back.
Hey, Seo-jun.
Mr. Choi, Seo-jun's had a bit of an
accident.
An accident? What're you talking about?
He fell during a game earlier today.
He's been to the ER. He has a ligament
injury.
Why are you only telling me now?
Seo-jun insisted that I not tell you, so
I had to wait until he'd fallen
asleep to call.
I'm sorry, sir.
Are you? I'm your boss, not Seo-jun,
understand. Don't bother coming to work
tomorrow. Your replacement will be there
tonight, so you should be ready to leave.
You believe he'll go without a fight?
You never know what Mun-do might do next.
Sir, I'm worried about your safety,
Shouldn't we be keeping an eye on Mun-do?
What's he gonna do? Kill me?
Boo.
Why did you sneak up on me like that?
You almost gave me a heart attack.
You came here, why are you so surprised?
What brings you?
Oh, Son brought me.
No, I mean, why are you here?
Something up?
Well, I want to go somewhere with you.
-Go where?
-A date. Let's go on a date, Cha Se-gye.
Date? You mean now?
Alright.
Are you serious? Your idea of a date is a
bakery tour?
The ring-shaped bread is famous here.
How did everyone catch wind of it so
fast?
I can't believe I expected something
else. Do you think it makes sense
for a man like me to waste his time
standing around for this stuff?
It's romance, it's not a waste of time.
I saw online that a date is spending an
enjoyable day with your beloved. Isn't it
enough for us to eat yummy food together?
"Beloved," you say? You can do
that anytime. On a date, you should
have fireworks, or at least a yacht
party, that sort of thing. This is
just mundane stuff.
I enjoy it though. That's why I like it,
because it's the mundane thing that
everyone does. But it's special because
we're together.
Whoa, th-that's a little on the nose.
Doing the things I enjoy with the one I
like to be around. It's something
I've always wanted to do. Is that a
problem?
No.
There's no problem.
So what now?
What other mundane things you wanna do?
Namsan? You want to ride the cable car?
Is this seriously what you want?
You sure?
-We can, right?
-No reason we can't.
We should! I really wanna take
the ride up. According to my notes,
Namsan has been a classic dating
hot spot for a long time.
Hot spot?
My Lovely Sam Soon, Episode Six. The
characters smash lips here, so these are
known as the Sam-soon Stairs And
that's not all. Boys Over Flowers,
Episode Four. Geum Jan-di went to Gu
Jun-pyo and opened up her entire
heart to him.
All those shows are ancient--
Of course, it's not just lovers,
High Kick Through the Roof, Episode
#122. When Se-kyung got Shin-ae
a free cable car ride by saying she
was 47 months old, it really moved
the hearts of the nation. And so--
Okay, alright, fine, fine.
I've arranged everything, so all you
have to do is follow me.
-This way.
-Hello.
Cha Se-gye, look at that.
Whoa. We're moving!
Be careful, Shin Seo-ri. You don't
want to fall off.
Fall off?
What is this? This is highly precarious.
I'll just walk. Let's get them to let
us out. Let me out! Open the door! Hey!
-Open this up! Hello?
-Hey, Shin Seo-ri. Shin Seo-ri. Hey.
Stop it, you're embarrassing us.
Who cares about that? We need to
save ourselves. Help us! Hey!
Let go.
Stop it! Jesus, I can't even make a joke.
What? "Joke?" You joke about a matter of
life and death? Stupid Cha Se-gye.
-Are you insane?
-I am insane!
-What the heck?
-His head.
-Man, how obnoxious.
-Yeah, she hit…
No way.
-Ugh, they're so noisy.
-Jeez, what's wrong with them?
-Is it a lover's tiff?
-Wow, seriously.
Why would you fight in here?
Oh, Cha Se-gye, look at that.
Uh, I'm here. Where are you?
Hey, I really need to use the bathroom.
Can you do me a solid and park my
van for me?
What? I'm not your valet driver.
Why would I do that?
Just shut up and park it.
Look, I'm not gonna go--
Ugh. Are you serious.
Full-time employee, my ass. As soon as
I get my paycheck for the month,
I'm outta here. The triple pay's not
worth it.
Ugh, why didn't you pick up your damn
phone? I was waiting.
Uh, well, I-- Uh, ex-excuse me--
I don't want excuses. Just take me to
Geumsonjongga.
And don't forget to order the spicy
chicken feet like last time.
G-G-Geumson… jong-jonga--
I'm tired, so don't talk to me
until we're there.
What are you doing? Come on, let's go.
Oh, Cha Se-gye, look at all these
wide open views. No wonder it's a hot
spot. It's perfectly situated in terms of
feng shui.
I think you're the only woman who comes
here and talks about feng shui.
Oh. Oh, look! Look!
Cha Se-gye, I know what this is.
These are love latches. They're tokens
left by lovers vowing eternal love.
So should we do it?
No.
Why? Let's do it. I know it's a little
childish, but we've come all the way
here, so why not promise eternal love?
Because they say it's for eternal
love, but these don't stay here forever.
If we come back later and find that
our latch is gone, I'll be a little sad.
That's why I'd rather not do it.
Why do you complicate things? It's just
for fun.
I'm more interested in the spyglass.
Where is it?
Wait up.
Calm down, heart of mine. Shut up and be
quiet, just be quiet.
Fucking bastard pricks, goddamn
motherfucking whack ass bitches. These
assholes are insane. I used to be the
favorite, the one everyone said was
flawless, and now look at this! They're
commenting that I have dead eyes and
pointing out my flaws? They're being so
mean!
What kind of jerks dare to say that?
The Kingdom of Women chat. Everybody's
saying I suck and that I'm a terrible
actress, but do they know how difficult
it is? I'd like to see them try
it! Damn it.
How dare they call you terrible? Those
fucking assholes!
Right? Fucking bitches! Do you have a
cold or something? Your voice is…
Oh, my God! Who- who are you?
Oh, uh, hi, hello, Ji-hyo. I'm Shin
Seo-ri's--
Oh, you're Shin Seo-ri's Supercar,
aren't you? What's Supercar doing here?
-The sup--
-Ah! Ah! Watch where you're going!
So you're not Supercar, you're Shin
Seo-ri's manager? And you're just broke,
not vintage? What are you trying to pull?
You should've said who you are.
Yeah, but I tried to tell you.
You told me not to speak.
Oh! Everything involving Shin Seo-ri is a
disaster.
My job was to drive you here, so
I'm gonna go now.
Oh, wait.
Yes, Ji-hyo. If there's anything else
I can do…
You're won't leave hate comments, right?
Hate comments?
You see, I've been in this business for
20 years, and I've met a lot of assholes
who are nice to your face and then
curse you out behind your back.
So let's not do that.
Yeah?
Got it.
Shit!
I'm not an asshole.
Cha Se-gye. From my window, I can see a
sliver of Namsan Tower, the size of
a fingernail. I was completely unaware it
was so big. I'm so glad we came.
Well, that makes sense, I guess. From my
place, you can see a forearm's length.
A forearm? You have that clear a view?
You've really made it, haven't you?
I've made it because I can see the Tower
clearly?
Of course. I heard that here,
seeing Namsan Tower from your window
is a measure of success. The bigger
you see it, the more success.
Shall we go to my place then? To see how
big the Tower is?
It's even better at night.
I've noticed you're always trying
to get me to go inside a home.
Yesterday, you tried to worm your way
into mine, now you want me to go
to yours?
Wait, my motives were entirely pure.
I just wanted you to see where I live.
Then why does it have to be at night?
Fine. It's because I'm lonely.
You're lonely?
Of course I am. I am not immune to
loneliness.
Mr. Cha must feel so isolated. His family
is awful. I think they were his aunts
and they came to see me earlier today.
I think they were trying to find out
what's going on between the two of you.
Talking about "the door handle to
power" or something like that.
I'm telling you to attach yourself to
him very firmly, like a stick of taffy.
Poverty in the midst of plenty, relative
deprivation. That kind of thing.
This man is opening up to me. Probably
only to me.
Do not worry. I won't let you be lonely,
Cha Se-Gye.
You won't?
I will not let you be alone. You can
trust me.
It's a promise, Shin Seo-ri. And it's
too late. Too late to back out.
-Here.
-Oh, thank you.
-For you.
-Thank you so much.
Shin Seo-ri!
Huh?
Why are you in such a good mood? What's
going on?
I'm glad you're here. For you.
Oh, wow. What is it?
Candied apples. I stayed up all night
making them.
Oh, you're even giving gifts. Your life
must be sweet these days.
You enjoy them.
Oh. Look here. Where is the overseer?
The director's on his way. Why?
Share these with him. Here. Don't hog
them all yourself.
Here's your costume.
What's this? A bribe?
Here you go.
Even the bribes she gives are tacky, just
like her. What's with this yakgwa?
They're not yakgwa. They're candied
apples.
I'm not gonna eat this. Who knows
what's in it?
Fucking bastard pricks, god damn
motherfucking wack ass bitches!
What if he writes something nasty?
I should've spoken more firmly with him.
Hey, Shin Seo-ri. I don't like your
manager. You should really fire him.
What sort of nonsense is that?
You've never even met Baek Gwang-nam.
Well, I've seen him around. I got a
shifty vibe from him. Stop arguing.
I'll send you someone suitable, so
just replace him, alright?
Worry about how your own face comes
across, you vixen.
How dare she…
The Chail Songjin Resort construction
still has a long way to go. Why would
he transfer you out of nowhere?
Our retail tenants are also complaining.
They all signed on because of you, Mr.
Choi, they're worried this will slow
things down.
What's the chairman thinking, making a
decision such as this?
He can't be thinking of putting
him in your place, surely? You all
remember when he fired all the CEO's
in HQ and every affiliate, claiming he
was cleaning up mismanagement. It was a
total bloodbath.
How could we forget? I don't care if he's
the chairman's grandson. We can't let
that jerk even set foot in the lobby
of Chail headquarters.
What made you suddenly change your
mind? I thought you wanted to
wait and see.
Well, the best defense is a good offense.
And the best offense is a preemptive
strike.
I can't believe it.
My ears are itching. They must be talking
about me.
So sir, how's it feel to be back again?
The air feels stale. Let's start
by replacing filters.
Calm down, everyone. I'm not going
anywhere. And I won't back down that
easily.
Mr. Choi, Mr. Park, Mr. Jung, it's been
a while. You're all looking much
better than when I last saw you.
Mr. Cha has just entered HQ.
You see, fishing is all about the art of
patience. When the time is right, the
float rises.
What brings you here, Cha? I've heard
some news about you through the
grapevine. I was told you're making
chump change at your little cosmetics
startup.
Actually, I heard you're making
pretty good money by snatching up
the best SME's and flipping them. Even at
Chail, you treated our executives like
cogs in the machine, so I guess nothing's
changed.
While we're on the topic, you know
what the trend is these days? Merit over
bloodline. Blind nepotism is an
outdated notion our business world must
leave behind.
Come on, that's enough The chairman
has always had a soft spot for Se-gye
because of the late Jin-woo. You all
know that. I'm sure there's a reason
our Se-gye has graced us with his
presence here today right? Even though
he hasn't been formally appointed
yet. Isn't that right, Se-gye?
Are you all done talking now? What's the
conclusion then? That I should know
my place and stay away from here? Too
bad. I'm a hothead, and the more you
trample on me, the more competitive
I get. You, Mr. Choi, our CEO of
Distribution. You call startups chump
change? Try making money before running
your mouth. I saw that sales fell 31
percent this quarter, didn't they?
Th-the price of the stock has now
stabilized.
Up next, Mr. Park, CEO of Chail Bio.
You remarked I treated executives
like cogs, yet you punish employees for
taking parental leave, forcing them
into contract work, am I correct?
That's your idea of "human-centered
management?"
Now, Mr. Jung Bon-gu, my eldest aunt's
ex-husband's youngest sister's
cousin, and CEO of Chail Chemicals,
you're next up.
I saw with my own eyes how you
campaigned for a position before you got
divorced, and now you're complaining
about blood relations? You hypocricy
is amazing, considering you're the
greatest profitter of marriage of
convenience.
What? Hy-hy-hy- hypocrisy?
Se-gye, stop this. You haven't been
appointed yet, so you have no right to
barge into a board meeting, even if you
are the chariman's grandson.
Please leave now, we have pressing
matters.
Oh, really? If that's the case,
then shouldn't you be leaving first?
It doesn't make sense for you to
lead this meeting, since you will be
exiled to the U.S. any day now.
I'll make it perfectly clear on my
first official day at Chail. Just how I
managed to get the position regardless of
the half-blood chaebol stigma.
How amusing. Has being on your own,
cosplaying middle class, helped you
gain perspective? Let me guess…
it turns out reality's not so glamourous
is it?
You can stop now with your fake
confidence act. I can tell you're
shitting yourself.
No, you're the one who's been acting.
I've never had the luxury of resting on
my laurels. You and I are fundamentally
different. You were born with a
silver spoon in your mouth, and I had
to work my ass off just to have a chance.
So you're a self-made legend then,
is that what you're saying? Isn't it
thanks to your family connections
that you're even here right now?
Although, I guess this is the last
time that will be the case.
Really? Do you think I'll back down
without a fight?
You should gain some perspective.
There's a limit to how much I'll let
you get away with. I wouldn't have let
things slide for so long.
-What?
-I kept quiet about everything that
you've ever done to me because I
felt a shred of gratitude for you saving
grandfather's life. But,
it's over now, you understand? I won't
tolerate you messing with my people
any longer so quit sneaking around and
come at me with all you got.
Tell me then…
You wanna go?
Oh, anytime.
Ex-CEO Choi Mun-do.
Noona. Why do you need me so urgently?
What's going on?
What happened between you and the vixen?
Uh, nothing. Uh, nothing happened.
Why do you ask?
Really? Then why is she telling me
to fire you?
She told you to fire me?
She was talking nonsense about how
you looked shifty, so I told her
to shut up. But you should be careful.
My influence isn't as strong as hers, so
be cautious.
-And keep your head down.
-Who fires someone because of that?
Okay, I hear ya.
Huh? Your costume…
Oh, my God.
You should've taken better care of your
costume. Wardrobe says they don't have a
backup.
Sorry, but why are you blaming the
actress? Someone obviously sabotaged her.
I'm just frustrated, that's all.
Ugh, this has thrown off the
entire filming schedule. Uh, okay,
we'll shoot the bedroom scene first.
Get the set ready!
All right, come on, get changed. Go get
your hair fixed. Come on, move it,
move it.
Shin Seo-ri's always causing problems.
She really has a way of messing
up the set.
Have you heard the rumors?
Is it time? They're getting the
bullets ready.
Biojei's about to rerate. Let's hit
that hockey stick.
They're like surveillance cameras. How on
earth did they know I was in the HQ
building?
Mr. Cha, how did the preemptive
strike go?
Basically, it was a near-death
experience.
There's a long way to go yet, so let's
take it easy.
You're right. Let's go back to the
office. That was enough of a warm-up,
I think.
First, we need to go to Hannam-dong.
The chairman wants to see you.
Thank you for inviting us, Mr. Cha.
I've heard that you've been taking
good care of my Tae-hee.
I have you to thank for raising such
an intelligent and positive young lady.
My deepest gratitude, I will take
good care of her.
I should be taking good care of you.
She sounds like she's already joined
your family.
Se-gye, hello.
I didn't know you had company.
Yes, come take a seat.
So, what kind of timeframe are you
looking at for the wedding? Tae-hee is
still young and focused on her career, so
I'd really prefer they take their
time and continue dating for a while.
I respect your wishes. We can
proceed with the engagment for now.
I don't mind if the wedding comes later.
You agree, right?
I hope you've enjoyed your lunch today.
If I had known, I would've treated you
to a proper lunch at a restaurant.
This feels far too casual a way to
treat a business partner.
I should be going now, I need to get back
to the office.
Sit down, Se-gye.
If you have something to discuss with me,
I'll come back another time.
I apologize for this disrespect.
I'll see him out, don't worry.
Se-gye, it's disrespectful to walk out
on my mother, you can't just do that.
It would've been avoided if you hadn't
come here today.
Is this because of her? Is that
why you're so rude?
I thought you were smarter, but I see you
have an awful memory. I made it
perfectly clear that I'd go through our
offices to call off the engagement.
Aren't you being disrespectful
by trampling over that agreement?
You know we can't just break it off
overnight. Mochang and Chail
have already signed an MOU, and there
are many things at stake.
That's why I've been turning a blind eye
to your constant disrespect. I don't
ever want to hear you talk about my
woman again. I already feel like
I'm hurting her by being here.
This is so unlike you, why did you
do this? And what made you cook
so many, huh?
It's fine. I'll eat them all myself.
Noona, that's impossible. Just leave
them, I'll take care of it.
What are you going to do?
I'll go to my old school and hand them
out to the students there.
Yeah? That's a good idea. Go now
before they go bad.
Where are you going now?
It's a secret.
What secret? I thought we weren't
going to keep secrets from each other.
I made something, so I came to
see grandma. I'm at the hospital to
-share it with some of the people here.
-Oh, yeah?
Sh-should I join you?
Don't be ridiculous. I've got to go now.
Is it just me? She hasn't treated me
any better since we've become a couple.
It's more concern than affection, if
you ask me. About your well being.
Especially your… stamina. I think
that's what she's concerned about.
I've gotten too soft lately.
It's time I showed my manliness,
Mr. Son.
Wow, thanks, how thoughtful!
I was just thinking that I needed a
pick-me-up. Thank you.
Oh, are these candied apples?
I'm so glad you like it. It's nothing
special. It will make you thirsty, so
get an iced coffee to go with it.
Here you go.
Oh, we'd get into trouble for taking
this.
Really? I'll go and get them myself then.
Hey, you seen the patient in 12?
She's been gone for a while.
Room 12? That's Ms. Nam Ok-sun.
Please give us a moment while we
check the CCTV footage.
SONGJIN GENERAL HOSPITAL
Where on earth has she gone? It'll start
getting dark soon.
Grandma!
-Oh, S- Seo…
-Where were you?
I went… to get some fresh air.
You should've told them you were leaving.
You scared me.
Gosh, why would that scare you, huh?
What am I, a child?
From now on, if you're going outside,
tell someone. And don't go
walking around alone, okay?
Jeez, this is like a prison then.
I can't even do what I want.
What's that?
Huh? Oh, it's nothing. It's nothing. It's
nothing. Don't worry, okay? Oh, hey.
Gosh, I said it's nothing.
LAND SALE AGREEMENT
SELLER
NAM OK-SUN
BUYER: CHAIL E&C
CHOI MUN-DO
It wasn't just a walk then.
To be honest, her mind has been
coming and going a lot lately. I mean,
given her age, it's unlikely to
expect much improvement.
Will you be paying in full?
Of course. Real men always do.
What?
I'm saying you can just charge everything
to that card. It doesn't have a
spending limit, you see. No limit.
Ah, I see.
I've paid like a man should, so
now what's the room number for
Nam Ok-sun?
Ah, let me guess… You're my Seo-ri's
boyfriend?
Yes, ma'am. We're officially dating each
other.
Your features…
are very nice. And manly too.
Right? Yeah, I've been told that many
times.
Uh, yes, thank you.
This may be presumptuous of me, uh,
but could I please ask you a favor?
Yes, ma'am, of course.
When my Seo-ri was growing up…
I barely did anything at all for her.
I was so busy running my restaurant…
she practically raised herself. So when
people said that she was mature,
she took it as a compliment. She liked
hearing people say that to her.
How foolish. A child should be a child.
A child mature for their age
is carrying pain.
So she may be a grown up, but inside of
her, she's a little girl.
I'm afraid she never developed a way…
to look within. I don't care about
anything else. Just don't abandon her.
Please be there for her so she…
doesn't carry that burden alone.
That's all I really want for her.
Yes, ma'am. I won't leave her alone.
I will never let her be lonely.
Then I'm happy. That is musc to my ears.
Yes.
Please don't worry too much, ma'am.
I've done very well for myself,
so she won't ever have to lift a finger.
Boys sure know how to sweet-talk.
I've got a way with words. I have been
told I like to run my mouth.
Oh, goodness. I can't believe I
haven't even offered such an important
guest a glass of water. You wait
right there.
Gosh.
Her granddaughter got so worried when
she suddenly disappeared earlier.
Tell me when. You wanna go?
That crazy bastard.
I knew you were a vicious monster,
but I didn't realize you could be this
shameless. You lured and threatened
a helpless old woman? Have you
any decency?
Well, well. Ms. Shin, you seem
very angry. But let's get the
facts straight, shall we? There was
no threat. We explained everything in
sufficient detail, and she stamped the
agreement on her own accord.
You took advantage of her confusion.
You pretend that isn't a threat?
Your face has always made me feel sick
to my stomach and now I know why.
You have the tongue of a serpent,
that beguiles and deceives. You are vile.
I have been away too long, haven't I?
So it was you. Kang clan, Dan-sim.
Your Royal Highness.
What brings you to my elder brother's
dwelling? No one has set foot here
in a long time.
Pardon?
This used to be the pavilion of my late
elder brother. When I was a young child,
it was my favorite place.
It also was my younger brother's
favorite.
This is my secret spot. What are you
doing here?
He used to tend to this place. He must've
missed our elder brother. That's the
kind of boy he is.
YEONGHWI CHAMBER
A gentle and kind soul. My younger
brother. He may have shut himself off
from the world wearing that half-mask,
but I know…
he too, had dreams of becoming great.
Dreams, sir?
Yes, that grew but were then buried
under.
I know you were close to him and
must find it uncomfortable
to be with me. I did not dislike my
brother at all. Just as there is only
one sun above us, such is the destiny of
those fated to live as royal-born.
Like Hyeon, I also have dreams. I wish to
be a king that will be truly worthy
of his subjects. Kang clan, Dan-sim,
will you stand among my subjects then?
How laughable that I was fooled by that
contemptible face and cowered in
fear for even a second.
Cowered in fear? Really? You?
I once thought that you might
return to me if I waited. That we
might meet again if you were still
alive. I waited like a hopeful fool, not
realizing I was being used. But
no longer. No more will I be manipulated
by such scheming and threats.
Well, none of it matters. The contract
was stamped, and the restaurant will be
demolished. All you have to do now is
pocket the compensation.
Listen. You have nothing to lose, Ms.
Shin. Oh, and… I wish you and Se-gye all
the best too. I'm truly cheering you
on, so don't take it the wrong way.
You're made for each other, honestly.
Cha Se-gye!
Choi Mun-do, you bastard.
You missed our little chat. You two
aren't on the same page, huh?
Shut your mouth before I rip it open.
This piece of paper? It means nothing.
And it's not even binding by law.
I'll throw you in jail for everything
you've ever done. So stay the hell
out of my way, or else I will kill you.
Why did you come here alone?
You should've told me first.
I didn't plan it. It just happened.
You promised me you'd stay away from him
and tell me if anything came up.
I already told you how it happened.
It wasn't my choice to meet with him.
Things just got complicated and--
I don't want you going anywhere near him
alright? I can't stand it!
Whatever it takes to protect you,
I'll do it, okay?
Excuse me? Who do you think you are
to say that to me? Are you already my
husband or something? Is that why
you treat me like a fool?
I didn't mean it like that.
You're worse than he is. You hurt
me more by treating me like an idiot,
pretending to take care of me!
Don't follow me. I don't want to see you.
I don't care about anything else.
Just don't abandon her.
You've come without notice.
What brings you here?
Sir, I have something important to
tell you about Se-gye.
How's your morning, Mr. Cha. Argh, Jesus
Christ!
I've had better ones.
Your face. Nightmares or something?
My life is a nightmare.
I'm such an idiot.
What have you done this time?
My mouth is the problem. Why did I
say that? I should have just shut up and
comforted her.
What a dumbass. Can't I control my
temper at all?
Well,
that's not the only thing you can't
control.
I can't stand to not see her. This is
no way for me to live.
Ah… I suddenly need caffeine.
A boss's love life is exhausting.
What'd you say?
Oh? Uh, sorry, I'm sorry I'm… uh…
Nothing, nothing.
The… uh, oh, ch-check, check the
center console. Please.
Have some of that to relieve your
fatigue.
-I stocked up especially for you.
-This supposedly helps with that?
Oh, uh, it seems to be very popular.
Man, I feel like my circulation is going
again.
What a selfish prick.
I want a guard positioned at the
grandmother's room. If anyone
suspicious is caught lurking, notify me.
And get out of the car. Right now.
Are you serious?
I did tell him not to follow me, but how
could he just let me go? Must he
be so petty?
Actually. I did say I didn't want to see
him, so I guess he had no choice.
Still, he could text or call. Why is he
tormenting me? Damn that jerk.
You're worse than he is. You hurt me
more by treating me like an idiot,
pretending to take care of me!
Ugh, you idiot. Why did you take
it out on him? He didn't deserve it.
I should eat something. I need my
strength if I'm going to fight and win.
Oh, boy. This place is going to go out of
business any day now. It's completely
empty.
It's break time. I only let you in
because you're a regular. Want to be
kicked out of here? Get out!
My goodness, you still have plenty
of energy. You could run this
-place another ten years.
-You rotten old man. You want a large?
I'm alone. Why would I want a large?
Your friend's right there.
What kind of asshole drives down
an alleyway like that?
Oh, Mr. Cha. Are you here to see Seo-ri?
She's out, left a while ago.
How long ago?
You know, Se-gye just makes me angry, I
don't know why. He's as stubborn as
an ox, never listens, and always
wants to do everything on his own.
When he was little, I used to hit him,
thinking I could win against a kid.
Looking back, I feel truly bad about it.
I wish I had just embraced and
nurtured him. I really do regret it.
He must've been lonely without a mom.
But instead of comforting him, I was
always riding him.
That's why I really want him to
have a family of his own, so as not
to be lonely. That's all I want for him.
If that's your wish, then you
musn't worry. I know too well how
wretched it is to be lonely. I won't let
him be alone in this world.
No, that's not what I mean. I don't
want him to be with a person just
as lonely as he is.
I don't want somebody who doesn't
have enough for herself to fill his
emptiness. I want him to be with
a woman who has enough to give and
also has plenty left over for her.
It's not that I dislike you. I'm just…
a selfish old man. I want Se-gye to
be surrounded by love, a big family,
in-laws who encourage him and who he
can depend on, that's what I want
for his life.
Is that too much to ask for?
There you are.
Hi, Dad!
I missed you Seo-Jun.
I missed you too.
CHA SE-GYE
Oh, pick it up. It's okay.
Boy, I missed you.
Your call cannot be connected and is
being…
CHA SE-GYE
Your call cannot be connected and
is being forwarded to voicemail.
Please leave your message after the beep.
Shin Seo-ri,
MISSED CALL
CHA SE-GYE
I'm sorry okay? Can you pick up, please?
I'm sorry.
I'll wait until you get here.
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
NAMSAN DATE
-Shin Seo-ri.
-You can't come in here. Sir, you can't.
Get out of my way. Shin Seo-ri, wake up.
Shin Seo-ri, wake up!
-Coming through.
-Make way, please.
Quickly, quickly!
Who'd have thought Choi Mun-do was
capable of this?
Chairman Choi Mun-do will now give a
speech.
He is facing public backlash after
carginogenic substances were detected in
Dynastie products.
She was found dead under suspicious
circumstances. And items belonging to
you were found at her home.
Your Highness, can you hear me?
-This place is…
-Bring the physician.
Have I truly returned here?